

△ 4070 Confederation Parkway Mississauga, ON, L5B 0E9

**(**647)-772-7983

vstnagab@uwaterloo.ca

Summary

Software product designer with a focus on web design and data engineering with over two years of experience in programming. Adept problem solver with a broad knowledge of algorithms and data structures. Wide exposure to a variety of programming languages and constant curiosity prompts me to learn and be open to new things. Ability to perform and learn under pressure has been developed from over a year of internship experience.

Experience



Technical Consultant @ Askuity Inc. Toronto, ON May 2015 - August 2015

Designed tools and built scripts in Python to automate the daily data ETL processes that integrate and manipulate Excel and BI (MicroStrategy) data sources to PostgreSQL and Amazon's S3 Web Services. Led the design and development of an internal Ruby on Rails application to monitor the data pipelines and dependencies. Worked with customers to define data feed requirements, data mapping and data synchronization. Leveraged clients' historical retail data and drew valuable insights from SQL and Excel to perform data analysis and apply statistics in order to support the Customer Success team.



Web Developer @ Purolator Inc. Mississauga, ON September 2014 - December 2014

Incorporated the company's website onto a new platform tool (Orchestra CMS) in Salesforce using Force.com's Apex coding language in order to achieve a MVC architecture based website with enhanced content management tools. Developed an employee database from internal security logs and took part in revamping the company's security identification card infrastructure. Worked on the design, development, and testing stages of various Purolator's proprietary web and mobile applications used as part of their major public services.



IT Engineer @ PRGX Corp. Mississauga, ON January 2014 - April 2014

Worked on team projects which involved programming database driven desktop and intranet applications in C# and SQL. Performed testing with various frameworks and enhanced the application optimize client audit processes. Configured various security protocols settings for the computers, printers, and other equipment within the office. Resolved PRGX infrastructure incidents and provided IT support to end users of PRGX's Canadian networks.

Education

## 2B Candidate for Bachelor of Computer Engineering

University of Waterloo Waterloo, ON, N2L 3G1

Skills

Languages: Java, C++, C#, C, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS 3, Ruby on Rails, Python,

PostgreSQL, VHDL, Assembly, VBA, Apex (Salesforce)

Frameworks: Android, AngularJS, Node.js, Rails, Bootstrap, MVC

Tools: Git, Gradle, Bundler, Visualforce, Microsoft Office, Active Directory, MATLAB, Microsoft Active Directory, Microsoft CRM, Microsoft Office Suite, Adobe DreamWeaver

**Projects** 

## Android GPS Application Development

Implemented an algorithm to track the user's position on a model of the physical world and accounted for errors in sensor readings. Participated in the project management, scheduling, testing, and maintenance aspects of the project.

## SmartWeather Android App

Shows the latest weather conditions and alerts on SmartWeather app by tracking the physical location of the user. Also has the ability to find local weather forecasts for the Canada and cities throughout North America .

## **LEGO Mindstorms**

Researched various robotic systems, autonomous machines, motors and sensors.

Developed algorithms and built an automated robotic vehicle that successfully completed obstacle courses. Fully tested, documented, and written a outstanding technical report on the automated system.